Anais Née Brown

Avenue Léon Mahillon 3 1030 Brussels, Belgium anais.nee@gmail.com

+32 487 91 98 75

Nationality: Belgian

CURRENT OCCUPATION

March 2014 - January/February 2015: Student in Web Development, Brussels

Currently undertaking one-year accelerated programme to qualify as a junior web developer. Passed entry exams in March 2014 and started May 2014. Confident user of the following programmes and languages:

Html / CSS / LESS	 Illustrator
• jQuery	Photoshop
Php/ Mysql	Bootstrap (basic level)
Drupal	Javascript (basic level)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

July 2012 - February 2014: "Groupon Belgium", Brussels

Community Manager

June 2013 until November 2013

- Dealing with and replying customer comments
- Creating content for updates and to social media pages

Quality Officer

January 2013 until February 2014

- Quality control of calls and emails made by customer service agents
- Reporting to quality manager and suggesting service improvements

Customer Service Team Leader

July 2012 until February 2014

- Advising and assisting team members on changes to working processes
- Answering phone calls and emails
- Following up contact with customers to ensure a complete service
- Compiling information files on cases for complaints brought to Belgian authorities

July 2011 - July 2012: "Du Pareil Au Même", Brussels

Store Assistant

Part-time shop assistant role in busy central Brussels clothing store, completed while studying for university degree:

- Providing quality advice to customers on products (clothing and shoes)
- Managing stock and presentation of shoe section
- Over time, took on more managerial responsibility, preparing rotas and mentoring new employees

July 2011: "Yelp"

Marketing assistant

 Writing reviews and short articles for the Belgian version of the review website 'Yelp' at its creation in July 2011

EDUCATION

September 2007 - June 2012: Facultés Universitaires Saint-Louis, Brussels

Bachelor's Degree in Germanic languages (English and German)

September 2000 - June 2007: Collège Notre Dame de Bonne-Espérance, Estinnes, Belgium.

High School diploma, orientation in modern languages

LANGUAGES

French: Mother tongue

English: Fluent written and oral

German: Intermediate written and oral Dutch: Intermediate written and oral